Finding Aid for the Delmore Schwartz Papers LSC.1005
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Books from the library of Delmore Schwartz
  - Latin selections = Florilegium Latinum. Selections in the original Latin edited by Moses Hadas and Thomas Suits; with translations, critical introductions, notes, and vocabulary by the editors. [New York]: Bantam Books, 1961, Call number: PA6116.H3 (Box 67)
  - High wire. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR6053.L38 H5 1964 (Box 48)
  - Prodigal women. New York: Avon Books, a division of the Hearst Corporation, 1942, Call number: PS3515.A273 P7 1942 (Box 48)
  - New poets of England and America introduction by Robert Frost. New York: Meridian Books, 1957, Call number: PR1225.H137n (Box 67)
  - New poets of England and America: second selection. English poets edited by Donald Hall. American poets edited by Robert Pack. Cleveland: Meridian Books, 1962, Call number: PS614.H26 (Box 14)
  - Seven short novel masterpieces edited by Leo Hamalian and Edmond L. Volpe; with an introduction by Mark Schorer. New York: Popular Living Classics Library, 1961, Call number: PZ1.H176 S4 (Box 70)
  - Generation X. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett Publications, 1964, Call number: HQ799.8.G7 H3 1964 (Box 23)
  - Immigration as a factor in American history. Englewood Cliffs, N.J.: Prentice-Hall, 1959, Call number: E184.A1 H23 1959 (Box 53)
  - Collected poems of Thomas Hardy. London: Macmillan, 1923, Call number: PR4741.F23 1923 (Box 45)
  - Which the justice, which the thief. New York, N.Y.: Avon Books, a division of the Hearst Corporation, 1965, Call number: PS3558.A63 W48 1965 (Box 55)
  - Celestial railroad: and other stories with an afterword by R.P. Blackmur. [New York]: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PS1852.B55 (Box 14)
  - Scarlet letter with a foreword by Leo Marx. New York: New American Library, 1959, Call number: PS1868.A1 1959 (Box 23)
  - Existence and being with an introduction by Werner Brock. Chicago: H. Regnery, 1949, Call number: B3279.H47 E5 (Box 25)
  - Lyric poems and ballads Translated by Ernst Feise. New York: McGraw-Hill, 1961, Call number: PT2316.A4 F45 (Box 14)
  - Poetry and prose of Heinrich Heine selected and edited with an introduction by Frederic Ewen; the poetry translated by Louis Untermeyer [and others] including 110 new translations by Aaron Kramer; the prose newly translated by Frederick Ewen. New York: Citadel Press, 1948, Call number: PT2316.A3 E9 (Box 29)
  - Doktor Faust, a dance poem: together with some rare accounts of witches, devils, and the ancient art of sorcery done into English and edited by Basil Ashmore; with an introduction by J.C. Trewin; with engravings by Hellmuth Weissenborn. [London]: P. Nevill, 1952, Call number: PT2316.D7 A7; Front flyleaf is torn out. Annotated throughout by Delmore Schwartz. (Box 70)
  - In our time; stories. New York: Scribner, 1958, Call number: PS3515.H37i 1958 (Box 14)
  - Moveable feast. New York: Bantam Books, 1965, Call number: PS3515.E37 Z475 1965 (Box 47)
  - Suicide and Scandinavia; a psychoanalytic study of culture and character. Garden City, N. Y.: Doubleday, 1965, Call number: HV6548.S28 H38 1965 (Box 25)
  - Herodotus: the Histories translated and with an introduction by Aubrey de Selincourt. Baltimore; Harmondsworth: Penguin Books, 1954, Call number: D58.H43Ed 1954 (Box 67)
  - Child buyer. New York: Bantam Books, 1964, Call number: PS3515.H439c 1964 (Box 7)
  - Magister Ludi translated from the German by Mervyn Savill. New York: F. Ungar, 1949, Call number: PT2617.E85 G523 1949 (Box 23)
  - Facing north. London: The Mitre Press, 1963, Call number: PR6110.N8 H6 1963 (Box 30)
  - Destruction of Lord Raglan: a tragedy of the Crimean War, 1854-55. Baltimore, Md.: Penguin Books, 1963, Call number: DK214.H55 1963 (Box 67)
  - Modern Russian reader: Soviet prose, complete with English translations by Andrew MacAndrew. New York: New American Library, 1960, Call number: PG2117.M5 1960 (Box 55)
  - American poetry and poetics: poems and critical documents from the Puritans to Robert Frost edited by Daniel G. Hoffman. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, 1962, Call number: PS583.H55 1962 (Box 52)
  - Philosophies of art and beauty: selected readings in aesthetics from Plato to Heidegger. New York: [Modern Library], 1964, Call number: BH21.H677p (Box 19)
  - Hyperion, or, the hermit in Greece translated by Willard R. Trask. With a foreword by Alexander Gode-von Aesch. New York: New American Library, 1965, Call number: PT2359.H2 A73 1965 (Box 45)
  - Holderlin introduced and edited by Michael Hamburger, with plain prose translations of each poem. Baltimore: Penguin Books, 1961, Call number: PT2359.H2 A6 1961 (Box 67)
  - Third day at Gettysburg: Pickett's Charge New York: Holt, 1959, Call number: E475.53.H697 (Box 17)
  - Compact Homer: The Iliad and the Odyssey in the translations of S.H. Butcher ... [et al.] Illustrated with reproductions of Greek vase paintings; with summaries of the omitted books, notes and an introduction by Mildred E. Marcett. Great Neck, N.Y.: Barron's Educational Series, 1963, Call number: PA4025.A1 B8 (Box 7)
  - Odyssey translated by Robert Fitzgerald; with drawings by Hans Erni. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, 1963, Call number: PA4025.A5 E7 (Box 67)
  - W.B. Yeats, 1865-1939. New York: The Macmillan Company, 1943, Call number: PR5906.H75w 1943 (Box 19)
  - Poems and prose of Gerard Manley Hopkins selected with an introduction and notes by W. H. Gardner. Harmondsworth, Middlesex: Penguin Books, 1963, Call number: PR4803.H44 A17 1963 (Box 7)
  - Last romantics. London: Methuen; New York: Barnes & Noble, 1961, Call number: PR595.R6 H81 1961 (Box 13)
  - Great Russian plays selected and introduced by Norris Houghton. [New York: Dell Pub. Co.], 1960, Call number: PG3245.H81g; Title page and first 48pp. missing. (Box 13)
  - Great Russian short stories edited and introduced by Norris Houghton. [New York: Dell Pub. Co.], 1958, Call number: PG3213.H68 1958 (Box 14)
  - Ordeal of power: a political memoir of the Eisenhower years. New York: Dell Pub. Co., 1964, Call number: E835.H8 1964 (Box 47)
  - High wind in Jamaica: or the innocent voyage with a forward by Vernon Watkins. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR6015.H874i 1964 (Box 14)
  - Don't crowd me. New York: Popular Library, 1964, Call number: PS3515.U585 D657 1964 (Box 47)
  - Classic New York: Georgian gentility to Greek elegance. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, 1964, Call number: NA735.N5 H78 1964 (Box 55)
  - Against nature (a new translation of A rebours) translated by Robert Baldick. Baltimore: Penguin Books, 1959, Call number: PQ2309.H4 A6213 1959 (Box 14)
  - La-bas. Paris: Librairie Plon, 1908, Call number: PQ2309.H4 L3 1908 (Box 54)
  - Master builder: and other plays Translated by Una Ellis-Fermor. [Harmondsworth, Middlesex; Baltimore]: Penguin Books, 1958, Call number: PT8854.E4 1958 (Box 14)
  - Hangsaman. [New York]: Farrar, Straus and Young, 1951, Call number: PS3519.J138h (Box 5)
  - Pablo Picasso [translated by Norbert Guterman]. New York: H.N. Abrams, 1964, Call number: ND553.P5 J253 (Box 36)
  - Best of everything. New York: Dell, 1965, Call number: PS3519.A453 B45 1965 (Box 38)
  - Fifteen short stories edited and with an introduction by Morton Dauwen Zabel. New York: Bantam Books, 1961, Call number: PS2116.F46 (Box 13)
  - Great short novels of Henry James edited with an introduction & comments of Philip Rahv. New York: Dial Press, inc., 1944, Call number: PS2112.R12g (Box 14)
  - Marriages: and other stories with a foreword by Eleanor M. Tilton. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: PS2112 1961 (Box 22)
  - Wings of the dove with a general introduction by R.P. Blackmur. New York: Dell Pub. Co., 1958, Call number: PS2116.W5 1958 (Box 48)
  - Art of the novel: critical prefaces with an introduction by Richard P. Blackmur. New York: Scribner's, 1937, Call number: PS2112.A3 1937 (Box 50)
  - Portrait of a lady with an afterword by Oscar Cargill. New York: New American Library, 1963, Call number: PS2116.P6 1963 (Box 50)
  - Ambassadors: an authoritative text, the author on the novel, criticism edited by S.P. Rosenbaum. New York: W.W. Norton, 1964, Call number: PS2116.A5 1964 (Box 51)
  - Notebooks of Henry James edited by F.O. Matthiessen and Kenneth B. Murdock. New York: Oxford University Press, 1961, Call number: PS2123.A4 1961 (Box 69)
  - Principles of psychology. [New York]: Dover Publications, 1950, Call number: BF121.J23p 1950 (Box 23)
  - Rise and fall of Nazi Germany. New York: New American Library, 1961, Call number: DD256.5.J3 1961 (Box 50)
  - Six Russian short novels: The overcoat; Lady MacBeth of the Mtsensk district; A Lear of the Steppes; Master and man; The death of Ivan Llych; Ward no. 6 Selected, with an introduction, by Randall Jarrell. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1963, Call number: PG3286.J27 (Box 13)
  - Pictures from an institution, a comedy. New York: Knopf, 1954, Call number: PS3519.J29p (Box 14)
  - Way to wisdom: an introduction to philosophy translated by Ralph Manheim. New Haven: Yale University Press, 1960, Call number: BD23.J313 1960 (Box 51)
  - Comments on Cain with an introduction by Anthony Boucher. New York: Collier Books; London: Collier-Macmillan, 1964, Call number: HV6245.J4 1964 (Box 48)
  - Lives of the poets. Garden City, N.Y.: Dolphin Books, 1961, Call number: PR553.J7 1961 (Box 14)
  - History of Rasselas, Prince of Abyssinia edited with an introduction by Warren Fleischauer. Great Neck, N.Y.: Barron's Educational Series, Inc., 1962, Call number: PR3529.A1 1962b (Box 22)
  - Sexual fetish in today's society. North Hollywood, Calif.: Brandon House, 1965, Call number: HQ71.J63 1965 (Box 7)
  - Spanking: sex or sadism? North Hollywood, Calif.: Brandon House, 1965, Call number: HQ79.J66 1965 (Box 8)
  - Some came running. New York: Scribner, 1963, Call number: PS3519.J711s (Box 18)
  - Love in a London flat. New York: Popular Library, 1963, Call number: PR6060.O6 L68 1963 (Box 55)
  - Ben Jonson selected, with an introduction and notes, by John Hollander. [New York: Dell Pub. Co.], 1961, Call number: PR2625.A3 H6 (Box 67)
  - Robber barons: the great American capitalists, 1861-1901. New York: Harcourt, Brace & World, 1962, Call number: HG181.J77r 1962 (Box 23)
  - Jewish war translated with an introduction by G. A. Williamson. Baltimore, Md.: Penguin Books, 1959, Call number: DS122.J723 1959 (Box 22)
  - Dubliners. New York: Viking Press, 1962, Call number: PR6019.O9 D8 1962 (Box 15)
    Copy 1 in box 15, copy 2 in box 14.
  - Dubliners introduction by Padraic Colum. New York: The Modern library, 1954, Call number: PR6019.J85d 1954 (Box 7)
  - Ulysses. New York: Random House, 1964, Call number: PR6019.J85u 1946b; Heavily annotated with holograph notes by Schwartz. (Box 9)
  - Collected poems [by] James Joyce. New York: Viking Press, 1957, Call number: PR6019.J85 A17 1957 (Box 14)
  - Critical writings of James Joyce edited by Ellsworth Mason and Richard Ellmann. New York: Viking Press, 1964, Call number: PR6019.O9 A6 1964 (Box 14)
  - Finnegans wake. New York: Viking Press, 1958, Call number: PR6019.J85f 1958; Missing title pages and first half of the book. (Box 14)
  - Exiles: a play in three acts, including hitherto unpublished notes by the author, discovered after his death introduction by Padraic Colum. New York: Viking Press, 1961, Call number: PR6019.O9 E9 1961 (Box 39)
  - Finnegans wake. New York: Viking Press, 1959, Call number: PR6019.O9 F5 1959 (Box 57)
  - Recollections of James Joyce by his brother translated from the Italian by Ellsworth Mason. New York: James Joyce Society, 1950, Call number: PR6019.O9 Z65 1950 (Box 58)
  - My brother's keeper: James Joyce's early years edited with an introduction and notes, by Richard Ellmann; preface by T.S. Eliot. New York: McGraw-Hill Book Co., 1964, Call number: PR6019.O9 Z649 1964 (Box 13)
  - Undiscovered self translated from the German by R. F. C. Hull. New York: New American Library, 1959, Call number: BF173.J7253 1959x (Box 68)
  - Parables in German and English. New York: [Schocken Books], 1947, Call number: PT2621.K118 P2 (Box 6)
  - Amerika translated by Edwin Muir, preface by Klaus Mann, afterword by Max Brod, illustrations by Emlen Etting. New York: Schocken Books, 1962, Call number: PT2621.A26 A83 1962b (Box 23)
  - Letters to Milena edited by Willi Haas; translated by Tania and James Stern. New York: Schocken Books, 1962, Call number: PT2621.A26 Z5513 1962 (Box 23)
  - Penal colony: stories and short pieces translated by Willa and Edwin Muir. New York: Schocken Books, 1961, Call number: PT2621.A26 P4 (Box 23)
  - Diaries of Franz Kafka edited by Max Brod. New York: Schocken Books, 1948, Call number: PT2621.K118 Z5E 1948 v.2 (Box 30)
  - Concerning the spiritual in art: and painting in particular, 1912 [A version of the Sadleir translation, with considerable re-translation by Francis Golffing, Michael Harrison and Ferdinand Ostertag] New York: Wittenborn, 1955, Call number: N68.K33 1955 (Box 45)
  - Honorable estate. New York: Avon Books, a division of the Hearst Corporation, 1965, Call number: PS3561.A824 H66 1965 (Box 54)
  - Nietzsche: philosopher, psychologist, antichrist. New York: Meridian Books, 1956, Call number: B3316.K38 1956 (Box 58)
  - L.A. 46. New York: Dell, 1964, Call number: PS3561.E37 L3 1964 (Box 56)
  - Yorkist age: daily life during the Wars of the Roses. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, Doubleday, 1965, Call number: DA245.K4 1965 (Box 56)
  - Profiles in courage. New York: Pocket Books, 1957, Call number: E176.K4 1957 (Box 56)
  - Strategy of peace edited by Allan Nevins. New York: Popular Library, 1961, Call number: E835.K48 1961 (Box 56)
  - Eros denied: sex in western society. New York: Grove Press, 1966, Call number: HQ12.Y6 1966 (Box 8)
  - Purity of heart is to will one thing; spiritual preparation for the office of confession translated from the Danish with an introductory essay by Douglas V. Steere. New York: Harper & Row, 1956, Call number: BV4505.K54p 1956 (Box 2)
  - Sickness unto death translated with an introduction, by Walter Lowrie. Princeton: Princeton University Press, 1946, Call number: BT715.K52 (Box 20)
  - Selections from the writings of Kierkegaard translated by Lee M. Hollander. Garden City, NY: Anchor Books, 1960, Call number: PT8142.A25 1960 (Box 56)
  - Branches of evil. New York, N.Y.: Macfadden-Bartell, 1964, Call number: PS3561.I49 S53 1964 (Box 53)
  - English in England: short stories selected and with an introduction by Randall Jarrell. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, 1963, Call number: PR4852.J32 1963 (Box 42)
  - Choice of Kipling's verse made by T.S. Eliot, with an essay on Rudyard Kipling. Garden City, N.Y.: Anchor Books, 1962, Call number: PR4852.E4 1962 (Box 48)
  - In the vernacular, the English in India: short stories selected and with an introduction by Randall Jarrell. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1963, Call number: PR4852.V47 1963 (Box 56)
  - Build-up boys. New York, N.Y.: Macfadden-Bartell, 1964, Call number: PS3531.O966 B85 1964 (Box 53)
  - Ungrateful garden. Bloomington: Indiana University Press, 1961, Call number: PS3521.K6585u; Inscribed by the author. (Box 30)
  - Langenscheidt's pocket dictionary of the English and German languages. Berlin: Langenscheidt, 1960, Call number: PF3640.K4 1960 (Box 8)
  - Langenscheidt's German-English, English-German dictionary. New York: Pocket Books, 1953, Call number: PF3640.L36 1953 (Box 57)
  - Marquise of O--, and other stories translated by Martin Greenberg; foreword by Thomas Mann. [New York]: New American Library, 1962, Call number: PT2378.A2 E5 1962 (Box 27)
  - Wheel of fire: interpretation of Shakespeare's tragedy introduction by T.S. Eliot. Cleveland: Meridian Books, 1957, Call number: PR2983.K6 1957b (Box 27)
  - Making of modern Russia. Baltimore, Md.: Penguin Books, 1963, Call number: DK41.K68 1963 (Box 48)
  - Yogi and the commissar: and other essays. New York: The Macmillan company, 1945, Call number: PR6021.O4 Y6 1945 (Box 59)
  - Made in America: the arts in modern civilization introduction by Mark Van Doren. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1962, Call number: NX503.K68 1962 (Box 27)
  - Adventures of America, 1857-1900: a pictorial record from Harper's weekly. New York: Harper & Bros., 1938, Call number: E178.5.K692 1938 (Box 36)
  - Hearth and the strangeness. New York: Pyramid Books, 1964, Call number: PS3521.R35 H4 1964 (Box 55)
  - Minister and the choir singer: the Hall-Mills murder case. New York: Dell, 1965, Call number: HV6533.N5 K9 1965 (Box 55)
  - Ben Gates is hot. New York: Dell, 1964, Call number: PS3561.Y5 B45 1964 (Box 53)
  - Golden urge. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett Publications, 1963, Call number: PS3539.E69 G65 1963 (Box 57)
  - Fables of La Fontaine translated by Marianne Moore. New York: Viking Press, 1964, Call number: PQ1811.E3 M6 1964 (Box 17)
  - Selected works of La Fontaine edited by Philip A. Wadsworth. Carbondale, Ill.: Southern Illinois University Press, 1964, Call number: PQ1807.W3 1964 (Box 69)
  - Poems of Jules Laforgue Translated by Patricia Terry; foreword by Henri Peyre. Berkeley: University of California Press, 1958, Call number: PQ2323.L13 A17 1958 (Box 17)
  - Miracle of language. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1957, Call number: P105.L35 1957 (Box 17)
  - Inside Daisy Clover. New York: Bantam Books, 1964, Call number: PS3523.L1735i 1964 (Box 53)
  - Outline of the Bible: book by book. New York: Barnes & Noble, 1963, Call number: BS475.2.L3 1963 (Box 50)
  - Ring Lardner reader edited by Maxwell Geismar. New York: Scribner, 1963, Call number: PS3523.L31 A14 1963b (Box 33)
  - Flemish painting: from Bosch to Rubens. [New York]: Skira, 1958 (Box 36)
  - Banking on death. New York: Avon, 1961, Call number: PS3562.A755 B36 1961 (Box 50)
  - Complete short stories [of] D. H. Lawrence. New York: Viking Press, 1961, Call number: PR6023.L43 A15 1961 (Box 28, 17, 68)
    Vol. 1 in box 28, vol.2 in box 17, vol.3 in box 68.
  - Complete short stories [of] D. H. Lawrence. New York: Viking Press, 1961, Call number: PR6023.L43 A15 1961 v.2 (Box 17)
  - Sons and lovers. New York: Viking Press, 1958, Call number: PR6023.A93 S6 1958 (Box 17)
  - St. Mawr: and the man who died. New York: Vintage Books, 1928, Call number: PR6023.A93 S25 1928 (Box 55)
  - Complete short stories [of] D. H. Lawrence. New York: Viking Press, 1961, Call number: PR6023.L43 A15 1961 v.3 (Box 68)
  - Etruscan places. New York: Viking Press, 1957, Call number: PR6023.A93 E75 1957 (Box 68)
  - Looking glass war. New York: Dell Pub. Co., 1965, Call number: PR6053.O74 L6 1965e (Box 8)
  - Call for the dead. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR6062.E33 C3 1964 (Box 47)
  - Murder of quality. New York: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR6062.E33 M8 1964 (Box 50)
  - Spy who came in from the cold. New York: Dell, 1965, Call number: PR6062.E33 S7 1965 (Box 54)
  - Nonsense books of Edward Lear with a foreword by Howard Moss. [New York]: New American Library, 1964, Call number: PR4879.L2 N45 1964 (Box 8)
  - Perspectives of criticism [by] Walter Jackson Bate [and others]. Cambridge: Harvard University Press, 1950, Call number: PN85.L47 (Box 6)
  - Overreacher: a study of Christopher Marlowe. Boston: Beacon Press, 1964, Call number: PR2673.L4 1964 (Box 39)
  - Kiss before dying. New York: Pyramid Books, 1964, Call number: PS3523.E7993 K5 1964 (Box 53)
  - Sunset of the splendid century; the life and times of Louis Auguste de Bourbon, duc du Maine, 1670-1736. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday, 1963, Call number: DC130.M15 L4 1963 (Box 7)
  - Splendid century; life in the France of Louis XIV. Garden City, N.Y.: Doubleday Anchor Books, 1957, Call number: DC128.L58s 1957 (Box 17)
  - Impressionism: biographical and critical study translated by James Emmons. [Lausanne]: Skira, 1959, Call number: ND547.L54 v.1 (Box 18)
  - Dutch painting [translated by Stuart Gilbert]. [Geneva, New York]: Skira, 1956, Call number: ND644.L42 1956 (Box 35)
  - Pablo Picasso, blue and rose periods text by William S. Lieberman. New York: H.N. Abrams, 1959, Call number: ND553.P5 L54 1959 (Box 48)
  - British poetry and prose: Shorter edition. Boston: Houghton Mifflin, 1951, Call number: PR1109.L5 1951 (Box 21)
  - Dearly beloved: a theme and variations. New York: Harcourt, Brace & World, 1962, Call number: PS3523.L638326d (Box 19)
  - Shorter Oxford English dictionary on historical principles prepared by William Little, H.W. Fowler, J. Coulson; revised and edited by C.T. Onions. Oxford: Clarendon Press, 1947, Call number: PE1625.M72 1947 v.2 (Box 3)
  - Shorter Oxford English dictionary on historical principles prepared by William Little, H.W. Fowler, J. Coulson; revised and edited by C.T. Onions. Oxford: Clarendon Press, 1947, Call number: PE1625.M72 1947 v.1 (Box 10)
  - Which Mrs. Bennett? New York: Popular Library, 1959, Call number: PS3523.I839 W45 1959 (Box 50)
  - Raintree County: --which had no boundaries in time and space, where lurked musical and strange names and mythical and lost peoples, and which was itself only a name musical and strange. New York: Popular Library, 1948, Call number: PS3523.O246 R3 1948c (Box 50)
  - No way to treat a lady. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett Publications, 1964, Call number: PS3557.O384 N69 1964 (Box 50)
  - Nylon island. Greenwich, Conn.: Gold Medal Books, 1964, Call number: PS3523.O48 N9 F64 1964 (Box 53)
    Copy 1 in box 53, copy 2 in box 57.
  - Life studies. New York: Vintage Books., 1959, Call number: PS3523.O89 L5 1959 (Box 55)
  - Craft of fiction. New York: Viking Press, 1957, Call number: PN3355.L8 1957 (Box 68)
  - Of the nature of things translation by William Ellery Leonard. New York: Dutton, 1957, Call number: PA6483.E5 L5 1957 (Box 21)
  - 9 short novels. Boston: D.C. Heath, 1964, Call number: PN6120.2.N56 1964 (Box 51)
  - Classical German drama translated by Theodore H. Lustig; with an introduction and prefaces by Victor Lange. New York: Bantam Books, 1963, Call number: PT1258 .L86 1963 (Box 57)
  - 19th century Russian drama With an introduction and prefaces by Marc Slonim. New York: Bantam Books, 1963, Call number: PG3245.M24 (Box 17)
  - Critical and historical essays selected and introduced by Hugh Trevor-Roper. New York: McGraw-Hill, 1965, Call number: PR4963.A16 1965 (Box 21)
  - Memoirs of a revolutionist; essays in political criticism. New York: Farrar, Straus and Cudahy, 1957, Call number: AC8.M145m (Box 18)
  - Area of suspicion. New York: Fawcett Gold Medal, 1961, Call number: PS3563.A28 A74 1961 (Box 54)
  - Cape Fear. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1958, Call number: PS3563.A28 E94 1958 (Box 54)
  - Damned. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett Publications, 1952, Call number: PS3563.A28 D3 1952 (Box 54)
  - Deadly shade of gold. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1965, Call number: PS3563.A28 D4 1965 (Box 54)
  - Judge me not. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1951, Call number: PS3563.A28 J83 1951 (Box 54)
  - Key to the suite. New York: Fawcett Gold Medal, 1962, Call number: PS3563.A28 K48 1962 (Box 54)
  - Nightmare in pink. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1964, Call number: PS3563.A28 N5 1964 (Box 54)
  - Purple place for dying. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett, 1964, Call number: PS3563.A28 P8 1964 (Box 54)
  - Quick red fox. Greenwich, Conn.: Gold Medal Books/Fawcett Publications, 1964, Call number: PS3563.A28 Q85 1964 (Box 54)
  - Slam the big door. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett Publications, 1960, Call number: PS3563.A28 S53 1960 (Box 54)
  - Clemmie. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett Publications, 1958, Call number: PS3563.A28 C54 1958 (Box 55)
  - Deceivers. Greenwich, Conn.: Fawcett Publications, 1958, Call number: PS3563.A28 D43 1958 (Box 55)
  - Deep blue goodby. Greenwich, Conn.: Gold Medal Books/Fawcett, 1964, Call number: PS3563.A28 D44 1964 (Box 55)
  - Wycherly woman. New York: Bantam Books, 1963, Call number: PS3525.I486 W92 1963 (Box 50)